http://www.microtracescientific.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
At Microtrace LLC, we strive to do everything we can to respect the trust customers have in our brand and our commitment to your privacy is no exception. We are committed to protecting and safeguarding the privacy of visitors to our Web sites.
This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect from visitors to our Sites. The Policy also sets forth how we use this information, provides other details about our personal information practices, and explains how to contact us if you have any questions or concerns.
1. Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used
Microtrace LLC only gathers personal information, such as, first and last names, addresses and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, personal information may be collected from you in order to get your feedback on our services and products. You may choose not to provide the requested information, but in that event the Site may not function correctly or certain functions may not be available.
In addition, when you visit our Web Sites or Mobile Apps, we may collect certain information by automated means. The information we collect may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, computer/mobile device operating system and browser type, type of mobile device, the unique device identifier (UDID) or mobile equipment identifier (MEID) for your mobile device, the address of a referring web site (if any), and the pages you visit on our Web Sites. We may use this information to operate, maintain, and manage our website, service offerings, and to provide services such as technical support. We provide additional information regarding our use of “cookies” in this Privacy Policy below.
2. Sharing of Personal Information
Microtrace LLC may share personal information with subsidiaries and affiliates. Any use of this information by the Microtrace LLC and its subsidiaries will comply with this policy. Occasionally, we will send marketing information to you.
Companies may be engaged by Microtrace LLC to perform a variety of functions, such as providing technical services for our Sites. These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions. However, these companies may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose.
Microtrace LLC does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties.
Microtrace LLC reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the Online Service, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety.
3. Children’s Privacy Notice
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
4. Access
You are in control of any personal information you provide to us through our Online Services. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, you can let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below.
5. Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies allow the website to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most websites, Microtrace uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your online experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our Sites on an anonymous aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the Site, to keep track of the items in your shopping cart if you purchase merchandise online, to administer certain contests and sweepstakes and to help customize your Microtrace web experience. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances.
Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the “Help” section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this Site.
6. Links to Other Sites
We may offer links to sites that are not operated by Microtrace LLC. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, and any information you submit to those companies is subject to their privacy policies.
7. Changes to our Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 25, 2013. From time to time, it may be necessary for Microtrace to change this Privacy Policy. If we change our policy, we will post the revised version here, so we suggest that you check here periodically for the most up-to-date version of our Privacy Policy. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.
8. How to Contact Us
Quality Department
Microtrace LLC
790 Fletcher Drive, Suite 106
Elgin, IL 60123
USA
(847) 742-9909
or e-mail us at info@microtrace.com
How May We Help You?
Contact us to discuss your project in more detail.
Search for:
News
Latest News, Publications and Media Coverage about Microtrace
Timmothy Pitzen Disappearance- Real Life Nightmare
Asian Forensic Sciences Network Guest Speaker
Congratulations to Brian Ford- 2020 Ernst Abbe Award Recipient
Article: Characterization of Aluminum Powders in IEDs
Forensic Science Week 2020
Book Chapter- Forensic Hair Microscopy
Article: Toner Particles as Forensic Evidence
Feature Article: Resolving the Source of Foreign Matter in Formulations
Article: The Analysis of 3D Printer Dust for Forensic Applications
Analysis of Microplastics
Profile: Microtrace Looks Toward ‘Nanotrace’ Evidence
Microtrace COVID-19 Response: Update (21 April 2020)
An Update from Microtrace Concerning COVID-19
CACNews features Microtrace’s painting of Edmond Locard
Microtrace Scientists Present at Pittcon 2020
View All News
© 2000 - 2020 Microtrace LLC. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy
|
Terms & Conditions
|
Contact Us
|
ISO 17025 Accredited - A2LA Certificate 5106.01
Forensic Services »« BackCriminal ForensicCivil LitigationPatent LitigationInsurance LitigationEnvironmental LitigationExpert TestimonyCase ReviewsTeachingProductsIndustries Served »« BackArt, Antiques & CollectiblesBuilding MaterialsChemicalsContainer and PackagingElectronics & SemiconductorsEngineeringEnvironmentalFiber and TextileFoodForensic ScienceGeological & MiningGovernmentInsuranceManufacturingMarketing & PublicityPaint, Polymers & CoatingsPetroleum & PetrochemicalPharmaceutical and MedicalMaterials AnalyzedLaboratory Capabilities »« BackLaboratory CapabilitiesAnalytical MethodsReference CollectionsCase StudiesAbout »« BackFAQsPhilosophyQualityStaffReputationOpportunitiesDirections & AccommodationsContactContact
